[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "How you are feeling about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, it's pretty -- it's pretty exciting and to think that I'm sharing with you, that's even more exciting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Has he been generous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "He's been -- he's been very kind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Will he be watching this interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "OMNEY: He's watching.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Is there anything you'd like to say to your husband on this special occasion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Hi, sweetheart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "NNS", ",", "RB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "You are talking to Mitt, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I am talking -- yes, not to you, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Both 16 at the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "He's a much more senior person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "And you've sort of fallen for each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Actually I was -- right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What do you think the public aren't seeing about your husband that they should be seeing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, to begin with, I don't accept the premise.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "What has been the most offended you felt as his wife on the campaign so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "You know, I think sometimes -- you know, what happened -- I will tell you, Piers, what happened to me last time, four years ago, is the misrepresentations about records and different things like that where they make you feel as though you're not being honest or you're not true to yourself which could not be further from the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "What do you think about the way that debate has been framed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, you know, again, I really meant what I said last night because I have been in every -- practically every state of this nation and I've been speaking to hundreds of people every single day and seeing people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Are you having words with Mitt's senior aides about their little gaffe today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "You know, this is the distractions -- this is exactly what happens in a campaign.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "What was your view of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "I laughed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"]}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNPS", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What kind of reaction do you expect from your shareholders?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Well, I think the backdrop of our meeting today is that Starbucks had record revenues and the stock price hit the highest level in its history today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Do they understand the problem and the solution?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Well, I think there is a lot of rhetoric right now because of how fierce this competition has been.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "And how much actually comes down to individual bosses of companies like yourself to take initiatives that spur the economy forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "I think that's an interesting question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "What is your ultimate superpower that you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "If I had to one, it's not one that is very sexy, patience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Who is the closest hero that has that power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I go for the original choice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 453, "question": "What about the rights of the guy he's killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I don't know, but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What about Trayvon Martin's rights?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "You're a parent.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Would it be different if this was a black shooter and a young white boy who had been killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Probably, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]